A Guide to the Records of the Fairhope Industrial Association and the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, 1893-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Oversize Bound Volumes-Separate from boxes
  - Minutes
    - Fairhope Industrial Association Executive Council Minutes (Volume 53) 1899 Jan-1904 Aug
    - Fairhope Industrial Association Executive Council Minutes (Volume 54) 1904 Aug-1908 Jul
    - Fairhope Industrial Association Executive Council Minutes (Volume 55) 1908 Jul-1915 Aug
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Ordinance, Rules, or By-Laws Adopted by the Executive Council (Volume 56) 1899-1947
- Rezner Vs. Fairhope Papers
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. I (446) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. II (447) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. III (448) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. IV (449) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. V (450) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. VI (451) 1985 Nov 19 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. VII (452) 1985 Nov 20 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. VIII (453) 1985 Nov 21 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. IX (454) 1985 Nov 22 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. X (455) 1985 Nov (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. XI (456) 1985 Nov (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. XII (457) 1985 Nov (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, Vol. XIII (458) 1985 Dec 30 (Folder 446-458)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 1-200 (459) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 201-400 (460) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 401-600 (461) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 601-800 (462) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 801-920 (463) 1985 Nov 12-18 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 921-1118 (464) 1985 Nov 19 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 1119-1277 (465) 1985 Nov 20 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 1276-1431 (466) 1985 Nov 21 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Transcript of Proceedings, pages 1429-1525 (467) 1985 Nov 22 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appendix, Vol. I, pages1-200 (468) 1985 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appendix, Vol. II, pages 201-400 (469) 1985 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appendix, Vol. III, pages 401-600 (470) 1985 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appendix, Vol. IV, pages 601-800 (471) 1985 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appendix, Vol. V, pages 801-1021 (472) 1985 (Folder 459-472)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Plaintiff's Exhibits 1-116 (5 folders) (473-477) 1985 (Folder 473-482)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Plaintiff's Exhibit 131 (5 folders) (478-482) 1985 (Folder 473-482)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Amicus Curiae Briefs (483) 1969-1979 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Amicus Curiae Briefs (484) 1986-1988 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Appeal Correspondence (485) 1986-1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Attorney Fee Proceedings (486) 1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Attorneys Correspondence (2 folders) (487-488) 1980-1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Attorney Fee Proceedings (489) 1985-1991 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Brief of Appellant-Appellee ' Baldwin (490) 1986-1987 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Briefs of Appellants (491) 1972-1978, 1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Brief of Defendants in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment (2 folders) (492-493) 1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Brief of Defendants in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment (494) 1991 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Brief of Plaintiffs-Appellees (495) 1991 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Brief of Plaintiffs-Appellees in Support of Petition for Rehearing (496) 1987 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Court Decrees (497) 1981-1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Court Documents ' Miscellaneous (498) 1985-1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Court Orders (499) 1989-1990 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Ruth E. Rockwell, April 4, 1984 (500) 1984-1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Gale W. Rowe, May 21, 1984 (2 folders) (501-502) 1984-1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Robert G. Mason, October 30, 1984 (503) 1984-1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of John Parker, November 1, 1984 (504) 1984 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Thomas H. Brown and John Parker, November 1, 1984 (505) 1984-1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Donald Winston Gooden, November 1, 1984 (506) 1984-1985 (Folder 483-506)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Claude Arnold and Ernest Bailey, November 9, 1984 (506) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Morris Ebenstein, November 5, 1984 (507) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Wayne C. Curtis, November 19, 1984 (2 folders) (508-509) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Sam Dyson, November 20, 1984 (2 folders) (510-511) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Jacquelin A. McKean, November 26, 1984 (512) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Jacquelin A. McKean, November 26, 1984 ' Advocates Notes (513) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of William C. Lucey, December 17, 1984 (514) 1984-1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Caroline H. Lindgren, February 1, 1985 (515) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Robert J. Potter, February 1, 1985 (516) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Matthew P. Dial, February 6, 1985 (517) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Rudolph John Rezner, February 18, 1985 (518) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Deposition of Paul M. Gaston, August 12, 1985 (2 folders) (519-520) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Frederick Ervin Boone, Emmett B. Gwin, Jr., and Allen C. Hoffman, August 16, 1985 (521) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Mary Gaston Godard and Charles B. Ingersoll, August 22, 1985 (522) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Bartlett H. Jennings, Jr. and Titus R. Mason, August 22, 1985 (523) 1985 (Box (Folder 507-524)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Wayne C. Curtis, August 23, 1985 (525) 1984-1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Sybil Tobias, Mark Williams, and Steven M. Zimmerman, September 10, 1985 (526) 1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Depositions of Donna M. Hamilton and Thomas D. Hamilton, November 6, 1985 (527) 1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Financial Statements, 1982-1984 (528) 1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Financial Statements, 1985-1988 (529) 1990 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Foundation of Fairhope: Principle and Purpose (2 folders) (530-531) 1966-1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Land Valuation (532) 1967-1979 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Legislative Committee Info (533) 1975-1982 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Lessees' Lists (534) 1977-1979 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Lessees' Lists (535) 1980-1981 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Membership and Improvements, 1979-1984 (536) 1984 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Non-Member Lessees' Lists (537) 1980 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Non-Member Lessees' Lists (538) 1981 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Membership Proceedings, 1964-1978 (2 folders) (539-540) 1984 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Membership Proceedings, 1979-1980 (541) 1984 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Membership Proceedings, 1979-1981 (542) 1984 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Membership Proceedings, 1973-1979 (543) 1984 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Documents Produced ' Miscellaneous (544) 1976-1990, 1981 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Final Decree (545) 1985 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (546) 1976-1982 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (547) 1982-1983 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (548) 1982-1983 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (549) 1983 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (550) 1983 (Folder 525-550)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (551) 1983 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (552) 1984 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (553) 1984 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (554) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (555) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Issues and Claims (556) 1979-1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Judgment Findings of Fact (557) 1983 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Motion for Partial Summary Judgment (558) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Motion for Partial Summary Judgment, including Affidavits and Exhibits (2 folders) (559-560) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Motion for Relief Incidental to the Implementation of Final Decree (561) 1986 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Motions to Dismiss Non-Member Lessee as Party Plaintiff (562) 1984 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Notice of Depositions (563) 1984-1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Notice of Pendency of Class Action (564) 1983 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Petitions for Rehearing (565) 1986-1987 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Plaintiffs' Brief to Rebut Defendants' Motion for Summary Judgment... (3 folders) (566-568) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Plaintiffs' Post-Trial Brief (569) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Plaintiffs' Post-Trial Rebuttal Brief (570) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Pleadings (571) 1979-1983 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Pleadings (572) 1984-1986 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Post-Trial Brief of Defendants (573) 1985 (Folder 551-573)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Presentation of Fairhope Single Tax Corporation before Joint Interim Legislative Committee of the Alabama Legislature (2 folders) (574-575) 1979 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Reply Briefs of Appellants (576) 1986, 1991 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Reply Brief of Plaintiffs-Appellees (577) 1986 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Supersedeas Bond (578) 1986-1987 (Folder 574-598)
- Rezner Vs. Fairhope Research Papers
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Affidavits of Individual Defendants (579) 1985-1987 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Charter Revocation and Dissolution (580) 1979 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Client Activity Questions (581) 1984 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Complaints (582) 1979-1981 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Constitutional Laws used as Exhibits to Brief (583) [1970s] (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Court Strategies (2 folders) (584-585) 1985 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Decree Study (586) 1986 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Depositions (2 folders) (587-588) 1984 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Depositions of Wayne C. Curtis (4 folders) (589-592) 1978-1985 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Dismissal of Hoffren Case (3 folders) (593-595) 1977-1987 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Morris Ebenstein (596) 1979-1986 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Equitable Approximation (597) 1984 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Equitable Approximation ' Land Transfers (598) 1979-1985 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Equitable Approximation ' Property Improvements (2 folders) (599-600) 1988 (Folder 574-598)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Equitable Approximation ' Property Improvements Distribution, 1966-1978 (2 folders) (601-602) 1984 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Equitable Approximation ' Specific Charges (603) 1984 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Fund Balances (604) 1985-1989 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Hoffren Property (605) 1971-1983 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections #23 (2 folders) (606-607) 1970-1984 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (608) 1981-1983 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (2 folders) (609-610) 1982 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (Source Copies) (611) 1983 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (612) 1984 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Interrogatories, Answers, Objections (3 folders) (613-615) 1984-1985 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Issues and Claims (616) 1979-1985 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Jury Selection (617) 1985 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Land Controversy (2 folders) (618-619) 1905-1992 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Land Deeds, 1890s-1970s (3 folders) (620-622) 1976 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Land Valuation ' Current Use (623) 1979-1991 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Land Valuation Taxation (2 folders) (624-625) 1983-1987 (Folder 601-625)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Lessees Association (626) 1978-1980 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Membership Applications filed out of conformance with rules (627) 1975 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Membership Petitions (628) 1980-1987 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Memorandum Opinion (629) 1981 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Miscellaneous (2 folders) (630-631) 1982-1990 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Motion to Consolidate; Status Reports on Williams, Tobias, and Hoffren (2 folders) (632-633) 1980-1984 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Notice to the Class (634) 1984-1985 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Original and Amended Complaints, 1979-1984 (635) 1984 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' J. Richmond Pearson (636) 1985-1986 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Plaintiffs' Exhibits (637) 1984 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Plaintiffs' Motion for Summary Judgment (638) 1985 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Rent Determination Methods (639) 1978-1986 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Rent Miscellaneous, 1963-1981 (640) 1981 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Revenue (641) 1968-1986 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Rezner Property (642) 1972-1985 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Settlement (643) 1984 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Settlement (644) 1985-1986 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Settlement (645) 1987-1990 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Settlement Proposals (646) 1985 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Source Copies (4 folders) (647-650) 1979-1984 (Folder 626-651)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Rezner Suit ' Research & Notes ' Township Plats (651) 1973
  - Fairhope Street Maps and Vicinity Maps ca. 1927-1976
  - Printed Miscellaneous re Fairhope, taxes, and utilities (3 items) ca. 1935-1976
  - Annual Reports Worksheets 1959-1965